Previously on The Blacklist...
黑名單 前情提要
We have credible intelligence that you're being targeted.
我們有可靠信息 你成了刺殺目標
Anslo Garrick got you to bring me here
Anslo Garrick騙到你把我帶到這來
so that he could attack this facility.
以便能襲擊這棟大樓
You're going into the box until the threat is neutralized.
你要去拘禁箱 直到威脅解除
Neutralized? Harold, do not make a stand.
解除? Harold 別負隅頑抗了
He means to take me, Agent Ressler,
他是來抓我的 Ressler探員
and kill anyone in his way or in his wake.
他會殺掉所有擋他路的人 或者他背後的人
Hello, Red.
你好 赤魔
- Where is everyone? - Captured.
- 大家去哪兒了? - 都被抓了
I think Ressler's in bad shape.
我覺得Ressler情況不妙
We're gonna go find those jammers.
我們要去找干擾器
10 seconds, Red.
還有十秒 赤魔
Wait.
等等
Red, I don't have to explain what happens now, do I?
赤魔 我就不用解釋接下來的事了吧?
You open the box, or Dembe dies.
你打開箱子 不然Dembe就得死
Come on.
快啊
system reboot complete
系統重啟完成
Yes.
好的
North Arlington Furniture Warehouse. Can I help you?
北阿靈頓傢俱倉庫 請問有何需要?
Hatchling 5591.
小鳥 5591
Stay on your knees.
跪下
I got the signal out, but I need a dispatch co...
信號發出去了 但我需要分配密...
Dispatch code...
分配密碼...
Cavalry's on their way.
救援就要到了
You're about to get your ass kicked off the planet, pal.
你們就快小命不保了 夥計
Want to bet I can drop you before you can get one shot off with that pistol?
信不信在你開槍之前我就能幹掉你?
Well, I'm gonna kill him now, aren't I, Red?
我現在要殺掉他了不是嗎 赤魔?
Open the box!
打開箱子
Go!
去看看
I killed him.
我殺了他
We need to move... now!
我們得馬上離開這兒
Aram! Listen to me... We need to move now!
Aram 聽我說 我們得馬上離開這兒
Hold it!
站住
Well, who might this be? Someone you know, Red?
這是誰啊? 你認識嗎 赤魔?
Please. Shh.
請了
Ressler!
Ressler
- Aah! Son of a bitch! - Look at me.
- 混蛋 - 看著我
I need you to focus. I need the code.
集中精神 我需要密碼
- What code? What code? - To open the box.
- 什麼密碼? 什麼密碼? - 開箱密碼
- Oh, God, my leg... - Tell me the code now.
- 天哪 我的腿.... - 馬上告訴我密碼
Do not give him the code, Agent Ressler! That's an order!
別給他密碼 Ressler探員 這是命令
Oh, come on!
行了
Telecom has been restored. They have an open signal out.
通信系統重啟了 他們發了個信號出去
In about five minutes, an FBI assault will retake the building.
五分鐘內 FBI行動隊 將奪回這棟大樓
Get out now. You might survive.
你們現在離開 或許還能活命
- Lizzy. Hey, what's going on? - Lizzy isn't available right now.
- Lizzy 怎麼了? - Lizzy現在沒空
May I ask who's calling?
請問你是哪位?
This is her husband. Who the hell is this?
我是她丈夫 你又是哪位?
I'm the guy that's gonna put a bullet in your wife's head.
我是要爆了你妻子頭的人
Hi.
你好
Who is this?
你是誰?
- Put my wife on the phone. - It's for you.
- 讓我妻子接電話 - 找你的
- Tom! - Liz, are you okay? What's going on?
- Tom - Liz 你還好吧? 怎麼回事?
- Are you safe? - Tom, listen to me! Call the FBI!
- 你還安全嗎? - Tom 聽我說 打電話給FBI
No! No, no.
這可不行
What are you gonna do? You gonna kill me?
你準備怎麼辦? 殺了我嗎?
You just saved my life.
你剛救了我
Circumstances have changed, Donald.
情況有變 Donald
If you can't save her, you're of no use whatsoever.
如果你救不了她 留著你也沒用
Look at me. Look at me!
看著我 看著我!
Agent Keen will die. Now is the time.
Keen探員要死了 現在是時候了
Romeo. The access code is Romeo.
Romeo 開鎖密碼是Romeo
R-O-M-E-O... Romeo.
R-O-M-E-O... Romeo
Anslo, what are you doing here?
Anslo 你來幹嘛啊?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品本字幕僅供交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
Sync: 有志青年
-=伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 一馬平川 喔哪哪 VJ 小蘑菇 小鳴 小V 校對: 喔哪哪 時間軸: 有志青年
****
黑名單 第一季 第10集 Anslo Garrick (第16號) 結局
Let them go, Anslo.
放了他們 Anslo
Are you pleading for the lives of the feds?
你替FBI求饒啊?
There's enough blood on the floor. It's time to get the hell out of here.
流的血夠多了 是時候離開了
Oh, I know what time it is.
我知道這是什麼時候
You watch out for Old Red here.
你們看好老赤魔
He may not look like much,
他看著不堪一擊
but I once saw him kill a Somali with a wire hanger.
但我有一次看到 他用衣架殺了個索馬裡人
Simpler days, Anslo.
那時候世界簡單多了 Anslo
Simpler days. Right.
是簡單多了
Bring her.
帶上她
She doesn't do anything for you, Anslo. She's dead weight.
她對你沒有用 Anslo 她只是個累贅
Do I look like I care what you say, Red?
赤魔你看我在意你說的話嗎?
Everyone get down now.
所有人都跪下
Coward.
懦夫
Knees.
跪下
Secure the area and contact headquarters!
守住這個區域 聯繫總部!
Don't move. We're getting help. I'm gonna get you out of here.
別動 我們叫人來救你 我們把你送出去
I need a phone!
給我個電話!
I have to admit, Red, I was starting to think you'd never come out of the box.
我得承認啊赤魔 我當時以為你永遠不會從箱子裡出來了
But then her. She was unexpected.
結果她來了 她可是意料之外的
Old boy's still got the touch, does he?
老男孩還是有一手不是嗎?
Well, whatever blows up your skirt.
不管發生什麼事
Hold on tight.
手抓牢
Red.
赤魔
Breach team 5! Identify yourself!
第五突擊隊! 表明身份!
I'm Assistant Director Harold Cooper!
我是副局長Harold Cooper!
Help these people get to the Washington Hospital Center's trauma unit.
送這些人去華盛頓醫療中心的創傷科
District ****
華盛頓特區總醫院
90 seconds to the drop. I need that chip!
距離交接還有九十秒 快給我芯片!
The emissary hotel in Chicago... Mr. Kaplan.
芝加哥的密使酒店 Kaplan先生
Hurry the hell up!
媽的快點!
FBI! Follow that ambulance! Drive! Now!
FBI! 跟著那個救護車! 快!
Give me your phone! Give it to me!
電話給我! 快給我!
- Hello? - Aram!
- 喂? - Aram!
Agent Keen, are you okay?
Keen探員 你還好嗎?
Sir! Are you... Are you with Mr. Reddington?
長官! 你... 你和Reddington在一起嗎?
I'm in pursuit, but I've lost visual!
我在追蹤 但現在看不到他們了!
I'm headed west on Constitution.
我正在憲政街向西去
Do you have a location? They're trying to pull his chip.
你查到他的位置了嗎? 他們在挖他的芯片
Hurry the hell up! Close to the drop point!
快點! 離交接點很近了!
- 30 seconds! - I'm trying!
- 還有三十秒! - 我在努力呢!
Just give me the bloody chip! Come on!
快他媽給我芯片! 快!
Aram, where are they?
Aram 他們在哪兒?
Okay, six blocks west. Turn right at the intersection.
好了 向西六個街區 路口右拐
Turn right! Right here! Right here!
右拐! 這裡拐!
15 seconds. 2 blocks.
十五秒 兩個街區
Get me that damned chip!
快他媽給我芯片!
Okay, you're close. He just turned south on 7th.
好了 你很近了 他在七街向南拐了
Okay, the signal has stopped moving.
信號停下不動了
He's right there. He's in the street.
他就在那兒 路中央
Yeah, this is the right location.
沒錯 就是這個位置
Dispatch, we've got nothing.
總台 我們什麼也沒找到
Agent Keen, did you find him?
Keen探員 找到他了嗎?
No, he's gone.
沒有 他不見了
We lost Reddington.
我們跟丟了Reddington
Oh, this shall be fun.
這一定會非常有趣
How did this happen?
怎麼回事?
Anslo Garrick was a known associate of Reddington's.
Anslo Garrick以前是Reddington的同夥
He came in with a tactical assault team. He knew the floor plan.
他不僅帶了一個戰術突擊隊進來 還知道這裡的平面圖
Then I have no choice. This task force is decommissioned.
那我就別無選擇了 你們這個行動隊解散吧
- Diane... - Do you understand what has happened, Harold?
- Diane... - 你明白發生了什麼事麼 Harold?
You obviously have a mole.
顯而易見 你們這裡有內鬼
We have to find Reddington.
我們必須找到Reddington
The only thing that matters right now is how quickly we contain this.
現在唯一重要的事情就是 盡快遏制消息的蔓延
This did not happen.
行動隊從未存在過
Reddington is, and always has been, a fugitive at large.
Reddington現在是 也一直是個在逃逃犯
Aram, wait. You can't...
Aram 等下 不能...
We're done. I'm done.
咱們被解散了 我的任務結束了
Listen to me... Red's alive.
聽我說... 赤魔還活著
Liz, this is out of my hands.
Liz 我管不了了
Okay, assuming... I could help...
好吧 假設... 我能幫忙...
- what would you need? - Closed-circuit feeds from the block around the building
- 你需要什麼? - 獲得辦公室周圍的街區的閉路視頻
from when Reddington came in, going back an hour.
從Reddington過來的時候 前推一小時都要
Supposed to hand off the security feeds to the new team of investigators.
安保錄像應該會給新來的調查團
I suppose I could make us a copy.
我應該能弄到副本
Thank you.
謝謝
How do you think Ressler's doing?
Ressler怎麼樣了?
He's in surgery.
在做手術
They're hoping they can save his leg.
他們希望能保住他的腿
Aram...
Aram...
we got to keep this between us.
這件事你知 我知
We don't know who we can trust.
我們不知道能信任誰
Yeah.
是啊
Emissary Hotel. How may I direct your call?
密使酒店 幫您轉接給哪位?
Yes. Hi. Mr. Kaplan, please.
你好 請轉接給Kaplan先生
He's not available. Can you be reached at this number?
他現在不方便 讓他聯繫您這個電話可以嗎?
This...
這個...
Uh, yes, I suppose.
可以吧 應該可以
Goodbye.
再見
The girl.
那個女孩
The agent.
那個探員
I want to know who she is.
我想知道她是誰
You came out of the box for her.
你為了她從箱子裡出來
Traded your life for hers.
為她不惜冒生命危險
Red Reddington placing somebody else's life ahead his own.
赤魔Reddington 將他人的性命置於自己之上
What makes her so special?
她為什麼這麼特別?
I learned so much watching you, Red.
跟著你我學到了很多 赤魔
You taught me...
你培養我...
Gave me a taste of the good life.
讓我嘗到好生活的滋味
But that's all I was allowed... A taste.
不過 我能做的...也只是嘗嘗而已
You're greedy, Anslo.
你太貪婪了 Anslo
You went behind my back, made deals you knew I wouldn't approve.
你背著我做一些 明知道我不會贊成的交易
What did you expect?
你還期待怎麼樣?
I suppose I expected something better than a bullet in the face, Red.
我想我期待的東西總比 打在我臉上的子彈要強 赤魔
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I...
- 你還好嗎? - 是的 我...
- I didn't know what was happening. - I know.
- 我不知道發生了什麼事 - 我理解
- Who... Who... Who was that man on the phone? - It's nothing.
- 誰... 接電話的男人是誰? - 沒誰
- What happened to your face? - I'm okay.
- 你臉怎麼了? - 我還好
Damn it, you need to stop. You need to stop.
媽的 你辭職吧 辭職吧
You need to walk away from this job before it destroys you.
在這份工作毀了你之前離開吧
****
打電話給我-Kaplan先生
Don't. Listen to me.
別理他 聽說我
Don't answer it. All right?
別接電話 好嗎?
Look at me. We can go.
看著我 我們可以離開
- Go? - Anywhere.
- 離開? - 去哪兒都行
Nebraska. We talked about moving there someday, at your dad's funeral.
內布拉斯加州 在你父親的葬禮上 我們說有朝一日要搬到那兒去的
Someday.
有朝一日
I got caught up in the middle of something.
我被一些事情纏住了
I have to take this.
這個電話我必須得接
Aram, what do you have for me?
Aram 有什麼線索?
I sent you the files.
我把文件發給你了
Our cameras cover five blocks around the office in every direction.
我們的攝像頭覆蓋辦公室附近 各個方向的五個街區
Okay, I'll look through them right now.
好的 我這就看
Don't bother. Red wasn't followed.
不用看了 赤魔沒有被跟蹤
He came in at 5:15. No tail cars, no eyes on the street.
他在5:15進來 沒有尾隨車輛 也沒人監視
Damn it.
他媽的
How did Garrick know he was in the post office?
Garrick怎麼知道他在郵局的?
My question exactly.
我也有此疑問
So I started thinking...
於是我就想...
What if somebody inside already tipped him off?
如果內部已經有人給他通風報信了呢?
- You found the mole? - No.
- 你找到內鬼了嗎? - 沒有
But I think I have a lead.
不過我有個線索
We routinely collect all cellular transmission
我們例行收集樓裡 和樓周圍所有的手機傳輸通信
So much data... I had to play around with various mathematical structures...
數據可多了... 我必須運用各種數學模型...
knots, multivariate polynomials...
結 多元多項式...
- Aram, the lead? - Right.
- Aram 線索? - 是的
I found a pattern in the transmissions...
在這些通信中我發現了一個模式...
a series of calls made from a burner cell.
從一次性電話打出的一系列電話
Each call was placed just seconds
每次都在Reddington抵達郵局後 幾秒內打出
- All from the same burner? - No. All from different burners,
- 都是同一個一次性手機嗎? - 不 都是不同的手機
but all the calls were to the same number.
不過都是打給一個號碼
I vectored the address to a private residence a few miles from here.
我追蹤到幾公里外 一個私人住宅的地址
The address is 8123 12th street.
地址為12街8123號
What?
什麼?
I'll call you right back.
過會打給你
As with everything involving you,
什麼事情 一旦牽涉到你
things are more complicated than they may appear.
就會變得複雜無比
If I could, I'd end this right now...
要是我可以 我會現在就結果了你...
Give you the horrifying death that you so deserve.
讓你死得慘不忍睹 這是你應得的
Then do it.
那就來吧
Mm. When it's time.
現在還不是時候
You see, sadly, this isn't my surprise party.
很不幸的是 我並非今天的主角
I am merely the hired help.
我只是被雇來幫忙的
My job was to get you to the venue.
我的任務只是把你帶到這裡
And while I would pay a high price to silence you forever,
雖然我願意出高價讓你永遠消失
others have paid much more for the chance to hear what you have to say.
但有人出了更高的價錢 要聽聽你有什麼要說的
Please.
請吧
Anesthesia blocks the impulses to the brain
麻醉劑能阻礙通往大腦的神經衝動
so one doesn't feel the sensation of pain.
所以人們感覺不到疼痛
The drug that the kind doctor is giving you does the opposite.
而這位醫生正在給你注射的藥物則相反
It enhances the impulses received by the brain.
它會加強大腦接收的神經衝動
When he's finished, the feeling of a breeze wafting against your skin
等藥物注射完 小風吹過你的皮膚
will be enough to make you beg me to kill you.
也能讓你疼到生不如死
Cooper.
我是Cooper
AD cooper
Keen探員? Keen探員 是你嗎?
Mr. Kaplan?
Kaplan先生?
What color is the sky?
天空是什麼顏色?
Red.
紅色
You?
是你?
You're Mr. Kaplan?
你就是Kaplan先生?
- Who else knows you're here? - Nobody.
- 還有誰知道你在這裡? - 沒別人了
- Have you phoned anyone? - No.
- 有給誰打過電話嗎? - 沒有
- Who is he? - I don't know.
- 他是誰? - 我不知道
Every time Reddington came to the post office,
每次Reddington來郵局
a call was made to this address... I assume to him.
都有人給這裡打電話... 我猜是打給他
He's been watching.
他一直在監視
When he got word that Red was at the post office,
當他得知Red抵達郵局後
he must have called Garrick to trigger the hit.
一定是他告訴Garrick可以開始襲擊
- I'll handle the body. - "Handle"?
- 我來處理屍體 - "處理"?
We need the bullets. We can't have ballistics traced to your weapon.
我們要取出子彈 不能讓彈道科追蹤到你的武器
Okay, wait. I can't do this. I'm a federal agent.
好吧 等等 我不能這麼做 我是聯邦探員
I have two directives...
我有兩個任務...
To protect you and find my employer.
保護你 還有找到我的僱主
I intend to do both.
我準備兩全其美
My team will be here soon. Find his car.
我的人正在趕來 去找他的車子
210 over 145.
高壓210 低壓145
103.7.
39.8度
Increase the dosage.
加大劑量
We're already 12 cc over the max.
我們已經超過最大用量12cc了
Then why isn't it working?!
那為什麼還不起作用?!
He's resisting somehow.
他在努力忍耐
I can stick him again,
我可以繼續給他注射
but if his heart goes into v-fib, we could lose him.
但如果他因此室顫了 他會死的
Stick him again.
再給他注射一次
I ran his face against the database.
我剛在數據庫裡對他進行了面部識別
What database?
什麼數據庫?
No matches.
無匹配記錄
The car is registered to Borderland Cargo...
車子登記在邊境貨物公司的名下...
a shell corp with a dummy address.
只是個殼公司 地址是假的
What about the GPS data?
GPS數據能用麼?
If he works for the man holding Red, then maybe he's been there before.
如果他受雇於關押赤魔的人 說不定他以前去過那裡
You have six addresses. Five are centrally located...
這裡有六個地址 其中五個都在市中心...
A motel, a church, two gas stations,
一個汽車旅館 一個教堂 兩個加油站
and a restaurant in Alexandria.
還有一個在亞歷山大的餐館
But this? This is something.
但這個 這個一定有線索
Why?
為什麼?
It's an industrial neighborhood, remote.
這是個工業園區 很偏僻
The kind of place I'd find for Mr. Reddington if I didn't want him to be found.
我要是不想別人找到Reddington 就會帶他去這種地方
Time for a road trip.
要開始公路之旅了
Armed lookouts.
他們有武裝把風的
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼?
Calling it in. We need backup.
向上級匯報 我們需要後援
Stay in the car. My orders are to keep you safe.
待在車裡 我要保障你的安全
I think we're ready here.
我覺得我們準備好了
About bloody time.
也該是時候了
We've got company.
有人來了
What the hell is this place?
這是什麼鬼地方?
He's not here.
他不在這裡
How are we?
進行得怎麼樣了?
He's ready for you, sir.
您可以開始了 先生
Hello, Ray.
你好 Ray
It's been, what... 20 years? Hmm?
我們有... 二十年沒見了? 對吧?
Tell me, Agent Keen, which part of "stand down" was unclear to you?
告訴我 Keen探員 你到底哪裡不懂"退出"的意思?
This wasn't my operation.
這不是我的行動
Fowler may have shut us down, but did you really think
Fowler讓我們退出 但你真的覺得 Reddington的手下就不會去找他嗎?
They did this without your involvement?
你沒有參與他們的行動嗎?
The only reason you're standing here
你能來這裡 唯一的原因是 他們足夠相信我 讓我加入行動
Enlighten me. What is all this?
那你告訴我 這都是什麼?
Some kind of operations outpost three miles from the post office.
離郵局三英里遠的哨站
Seems to be manned by the same people
應該就是由那些侵入我們大樓 綁架了Reddington的人駐守的
That doesn't concern you?
您不關心嗎?
I lost a dozen people today, Keen!
我今天失去了很多人員 Keen!
That isn't on you. It's on me.
這不會算在你身上 但會算在我身上
No one wants the men who did this more than I do.
沒人比我更想抓獲這些罪犯
But riding shotgun on an unsanctioned massacre isn't the way to get it done.
但我們不能未經批准 就用霰彈槍大開殺戒
- Excuse me, Director Cooper? - What is it?
- 打擾一下 Cooper副局? - 什麼事?
There's something you need to see.
你得看看這個
I thought I was clear... This task force is done.
我以為我說得很清楚了... 這個行動隊已經解散了
I think you'll reconsider.
你會重新考慮這一決策的
Why in God's name would I do that?
你憑什麼覺得我會這麼做?
Because this isn't just about Reddington anymore.
因為這已經不僅僅關乎到Reddington了
Agent Keen located a surveillance outpost a few miles from here.
Keen探員發現了 幾英里外的一個監視哨站
Next-gen tech, better than anything we have in the field.
新一代技術 比我們現有的都要好
- Surveillance on what? - Us.
- 監視什麼? - 我們
They've been watching this task force for months...
我們已經被盯上好幾個月了...
Phone taps, communications logs... We're not sure to what extent.
電話監聽 通訊日誌 我不清楚他們究竟聽到多少
We were able to recover very little.
我們能恢復的數據非常有限
The equipment and data were rigged to self-destruct.
他們的設備和數據 設置了自我銷毀程序
I don't understand. How is this even possible?
我不明白 這怎麼可能?
Something else you should know.
還有別的事情你需要知道
They've been watching you, too.
他們同樣也在監視你
All right, that's enough. Let him down.
夠了 放他下來
Come on. Get him a chair.
快點 給他個椅子坐
I don't understand, Ray.
我不明白 Ray
None of this had to happen.
這一切都沒必要發生的
I thought we had an arrangement.
我還以為咱們達成共識了
We do.
是啊
Eh, I don't know.
可是我不確定
The people I represent, they're... they're nervous.
我背後的那些人... 他們很緊張
We don't know what to think.
我們不知道該怎麼看這事兒
We could've killed you.
我們完全可以殺了你
I don't mean today. I mean any day.
我指的不是今天 而是之前隨便某一天
I mean every day for the past two decades.
過去二十年裡的任何一天
But we don't.
但我們沒有
We know what you have, Ray.
我們知道你掌握的東西 Ray
And we know what'll happen to it if you turn up dead.
我也知道如果你死了 你掌握的東西會怎樣
So we do nothing. We let you live.
所有我們沒動你 我們讓你活著
And in exchange, we... we trust that our secret remains secret.
作為交換 我們... 我們相信你可以替我們保守秘密
- Nothing has changed. - Oh, no. I'd say everything's changed.
- 什麼都沒變 - 不 我看一切都變了
Everything changed the minute you surrendered to the FBI.
你投靠FBI的那一刻 一切就都改變了
Did you think we wouldn't know?
你真以為我們會不知道?
Maybe you wanted to change our arrangement.
也許你想改改我們之間的協議
Maybe you thought you could turn yourself in
也許你覺得自首之後
and, uh, find some new friends to protect you.
能找到新朋友來保護你
- Maybe you plan to expose us. - No.
- 也許你計劃揭露我們 - 當然不
What have you told, Ray?
你都說了些什麼 Ray?
Nothing.
什麼都沒說
Then what the hell are you doing here?
那你他媽的在這兒幹嘛呢?
My reasons have n-nothing to do with you.
我的原因和你們沒關係
Well, I hope so. I really do.
好吧 我也希望是這樣 真的
Because I've always liked you, Ray.
畢竟我一直都挺喜歡你的 Ray
You're a pain in my neck, but...
你就像一個疙瘩在我心上 但是...
I like you.
我喜歡你
Just know this...
你要知道的是...
You were walking in the park this morning.
今天早上你在公園散步時...
We could've taken you then.
我們完全可以那時就拿下你
Instead, we dragged you from the safety and security
相反 我們把你從你自以為 可以保你周全的朋友身邊拽過來
Why would we do a thing like that?
我們為什麼要這樣做?
To make it abundantly clear...
就是為了讓你透徹地明白
There's nowhere you can go...
你無處可躲...
There's no one you can trust to keep you from us.
別指望任何人能阻止我們抓到你
You were there? When Reddington's people took the building?
Reddington的人拿下那棟樓時你也在?
- How many people were killed? - At least six.
- 有多少人死亡? - 至少六個
It was an outpost. Professionals.
那是個哨站 人員都是專業的
These people were highly trained.
這些人經過專門訓練
Like Garrick.
就像Garrick
- What's all this? - A waste of time.
- 這都是些什麼? - 浪費時間
By Cooper's directive, I reached out to a few of our colleagues at the Agency,
根據Cooper的指示 我聯繫到CIA的幾個同事
informed them of our situation, and offered to contact
告訴了他們有關我們的情況 並表示願意接觸
my counterparts at the other black sites to share intel.
我在其他黑點的線人 表示願意共享情報
All these names are redacted.
這些名字都蓋住了
So much for inter-agency cooperation.
情報機構合作也就這樣了
You really think that Garrick had someone on the inside?
你真覺得Garrick在內部有人?
It's possible.
有可能
The only one beyond suspicion is Ressler,
唯一沒有嫌疑的就是Ressler
unless he used Garrick to shoot him in the leg to cover his tracks.
除非他故意讓Garrick射中腿 好避免大家的懷疑
- Is he still in surgery? - Four hours and counting.
- 他還在手術中? - 四個小時了 還在繼續
****
站點概覽
Hollins Ferry Road. I know that address.
Hollins Ferry路 我知道這個地址
It says DCM... What does that mean?
DCM... 什麼意思?
Decommissioned.
已廢棄
Here I am trying to help, and the only names that aren't blacked out
我也想幫忙 可是沒被蓋住的名字 都是已經廢棄的站點
Is that a church?
這是個教堂嗎?
Well, that's the cover story.
教堂只是個幌子
- I'm gonna need satellite access to this address. - Why?
- 我需要這個地址的衛星圖像 - 為什麼?
Because I think this might be where they're holding Reddington.
因為我覺得這可能 就是Reddington被關押的地方
- Is this in Franklin Square? - Yeah. Why?
- 這是在富蘭克林廣場嗎? - 對 怎麼了?
The ambulance that was used to abduct Reddington
在距離這裡2.5英里的一個車庫裡
they found burning in a garage a quarter mile from there.
發現了被燒燬的 綁架Reddington的救護車
I think we found Reddington.
我想我們找到Reddington了
Where?
哪兒?
A church in Baltimore... A decommissioned black site.
巴爾的摩的一座教堂... 是個廢棄的黑點
A black site? You think that's where they're holding Reddington?
黑點? 你認為那是Reddington 被關押的地方?
It makes sense. It's the last place we would think of.
很合情理 這是我們最不會想到的地方
And if he knew about this site, he'd know about others.
而且如果他知道這個站點 他也會知道其他站點
What about it, Diane? I need an answer.
你怎麼看 Diane? 我需要你的回答
Are we shut down or not?
我們還要解散嗎?
You should go, sir.
你該走了 先生
- I'll take care of Reddington. - No.
- 我可以搞定Reddington - 不
We had a deal.
我們說好的
I delivered him for interrogation.
我把他帶到這兒讓你審問
- I took that risk because you promised... - I know what we promised.
- 我冒險是因為你答應... - 我知道我們的約定
What I don't know is whether he's telling the truth.
但我不知道他是否說了實話
If you kill him, it could trigger whatever he has in place.
如果你殺了他 會激發他設置好的圈套
With all due respect, sir, that's not my problem.
恕我直言 先生 那不關我的事
- Excuse me? - I lost a lot of men today...
- 什麼? - 我今天失去了很多兄弟...
Couple of good ones.
好多都是精英
You had your talk.
你已經審問完了
Now it's my turn.
現在輪到我了
Just you and me again, Red.
又剩咱們倆了 赤魔
Just like the old days.
和以前一樣
Oh, give it a rest. We both know Fitch won't let you finish it.
算了 咱倆都明白 Fitch不會讓你這樣做的
That's as may be.
可能吧
But you know what I can do, though, Red?
但你知道我能做什麼 對吧 赤魔?
I can find Lizzy.
我能找到Lizzy
I can hurt her. I can make her suffer.
傷害她 折磨她
And when I'm finished, I can kill her.
折磨夠了 再殺了她
Sometimes you just have to take what you can in this crazy world.
在這個瘋狂的世界 有時候得盡其所能
Guess who taught me that, Red.
猜猜是誰教我的 赤魔?
You did.
是你
What? No smart quips?
怎麼了? 你的名言警句呢? 怎麼不說了?
You're not actually feeling something, are you, Red?
你不是真的有感覺了吧 赤魔?
Regret.
我感到後悔
He was here.
他之前在這兒
In what world is any of this okay?
這種事你覺得無所謂嗎?
The fact that you don't see that, that this is somehow normal to you...
實際上 你不明白 這對你已經是家常便飯了...
- I'm sorry. - A man told me that he was gonna kill you.
- 對不起 - 有人告訴我他要殺了你
I've been attacked, I've been accused of murder, and now people are watching us.
我已經被攻擊過 被指控謀殺 而且現在又有人監視我們
Apparently, there are cameras in our bedroom.
顯然我們的臥室裝了攝像頭
- They're gone. - Do you believe that?
- 他們撤了 - 你信嗎?
I need us together... and safe.
我們得在一起...平平安安的
I meant what I said earlier.
我之前說的是認真的
We need to leave this place.
我們得離開這裡
Audrey? Hey. What are you doing here?
Audrey? 嗨 你怎麼來啦?
I got a call. You okay?
我接到一個電話 你還好嗎?
Yeah. Yeah, long story. Uh...
是的 一言難盡...
I'm fine.
我很好
- They called you? - Bureau did.
- 他們給你打電話了? - FBI打的
I guess I'm still on as your "next of kin."
我想我還在你的"近親"名單上吧
Right. Your name's still on that list.
不錯 你名字還在名單上
I meant to take it off. I've just been so busy, I...
我本來想去掉的 但一直都這麼忙 我...
No, no, no. It's okay. I get it.
不 沒事的 我懂
So, you're okay?
你沒事吧?
You're engaged?
你訂婚了?
It's crazy, right?
很瘋狂 對吧?
Tell me he's fat and unemployed.
告訴我他是又胖又沒工作
He's fat and unemployed.
他又胖又沒工作
Mind staying for a few minutes?
不介意多待一會兒吧?
He was there.
他之前確實在那兒
- Lab tests confirm the blood was Reddington's. - Which means?
- 實驗室確定了血是Reddington的 - 所以呢?
As far as we can tell, he killed his captor and escaped.
我們至少知道 他殺了抓他的人而且逃脫了
- Then why aren't you out hunting him down? - I'm sorry?
- 那你為什麼不去追捕他? - 什麼?
I thought we were in the "cover our asses" business, in containment mode.
我以為我們要掩蓋事實控制局勢
That ship has sailed, Harold.
現在不是了 Harold
Someone is surveilling us, and we don't know who.
有人在監視我們 我們不知道是誰
- Reddington does. - You don't know that.
- 但Reddington知道 - 這你不能確定
We have a mole.
我們有內鬼
That mole leaked intel leading to the abduction and torture of Reddington.
這個內鬼洩露了消息導致 Reddington被綁架受折磨
It's a simple math problem, Harold.
這太簡單了 Harold
Whoever is after Reddington is after us,
抓Reddington的人也在監視我們
and that means, as far as I'm concerned,
所以 依我看
that Reddington still has real value.
Reddington仍然有實際價值
The unit has a new focus... Finding him.
你們這個小組有了新目標...找到他
As of this moment,
從現在開始
the only target on the blacklist is Raymond Reddington.
在黑名單上唯一的目標是 Raymond Reddington
It's done.
搞定了
Hello?
喂?
Lizzy.
Lizzy
Red.
赤魔
Where are you?
你在哪兒?
Gone for a short while.
我得離開一段時間
Dembe's looking for you. He says it's urgent.
Dembe一直在找你 他說很緊急
Dembe will have to wait.
Dembe得等著了
Lizzy...
Lizzy...
I want you to know, wherever I am, whatever I'm doing,
你要知道 無論我在哪兒 無論我在做什麼
if you are in need, I will be there.
只要你需要 我就會出現
The task force, Cooper... They're searching for you.
行動隊 Cooper... 他們在找你
What should I tell them?
我應該怎麼說?
- I have to go. - Wait.
- 我得走了 - 等等
One question, please.
拜託回答我一個問題
It's about my father.
關於我父親的
Growing up, Sam... He raised me like his own.
從小到大 Sam... 他把我當親生女兒撫養
He was...
他曾是...
my whole world.
我的整個世界
But he wasn't my father.
但他不是我的親生父親
What is the question, Lizzy?
你要問什麼 Lizzy?
Are you my father?
你是我父親嗎?
No.
不是
Lizzy...
Lizzy...
be careful of your husband.
小心你丈夫
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 一馬平川 喔哪哪 VJ 小蘑菇 小鳴 小V 校對: 喔哪哪 時間軸: 有志青年
Sync: 有志青年
-------------------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 -------------------------------------- 黑名單 第一季 第10集 完 大家冬歇愉快